Council on Foreign Relations Records: Studies Department Series, 1918-2004: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Subseries 3B: Records of Groups, 1918-1996; 91.12 linear feet 219 boxes
  - Post-1973 Study Groups, 1959-2005; 93 boxes (1 partial)
    - Discussion Group on Congress and Foreign Policy, with Carnegie Endowment for International Peace (First Meeting, 1979 October 2), 1979-1980, 1 folder (Box 228, Folder 8)
    - Study Group on Military Factors in African Politics (First Meeting, 1979 October 16), 1979-1980, 3 folders (Box 229, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Discussion Group on the Role of U.S. Labor in International Economy (First Meeting, ), 1979 October 17; 1977-1980; 3 folders (Box 229, Folder 4 to 6)
    - Study Group on Domestic Sources of Soviet Foreign Policy (First Meeting, 1979 October 25), 1979-1980, 3 folders (Box 230, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Discussion Group on U.S.-Soviet Economic Relations (First Meeting, 1979 November 15), 1979-1980, 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - Soviet Policy in East Europe (First Meeting, 1979 November 16), 3 folders
      - Manuscript Correspondence, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 5)
      - Manuscript Correspondence, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 6)
      - Workshop, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 7)
    - Study Group on the Soviet Union and Global Issues (First Meeting, 1979 December 4), 1979-1980, 3 folders (Box 231, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Discussion Group on Nuclear Non-Proliferation (First Meeting, 1979 December 5), 1979-1980, 2 folders (Box 231, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Discussion Group on U.S.-Mexican Relations (First Meeting, 1980 January 14), 1979-1981, 1 folder (Box 231, Folder 6)
    - Discussion Group on U.S.-West European Relations (First Meeting, 1980 January 29), 1979-1981, 1 folder (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Discussion Group on the Middle East (First Meeting, 1980 January 31), 1979-1980, 1 folder (Box 232, Folder 2)
    - Discussion Group on the Internationalization of American Banking (First Meeting, 1980 February 4), 1979-1980, 2 folders (Box 232, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Study Group on International Financial Institutions (First Meeting, 1980 February 27), 1979-1980, 1 folder (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - Discussion Group on the Horn of Africa and Persian Gulf: Africa and the Middle East (First Meeting, 1980 March 12), 1979-1980, 1 folder (Box 232, Folder 6)
    - Industrial Policy Review Group (First Meeting, 1980 April 21), 1980-1981, 1 folder (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Study Group on the U.S. and the Southern Cone, 1980 May 19; 1 folder (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - United States Policy toward the Soviet Union (First Meeting, 1980 October 3), 1980-1981, 4 folders (Box 233, Folder 3 to 6)
    - United States Policy toward the Soviet Union (First Meeting, 1980 October 3), 1980-1981, 2 folders (Box 234, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Discussion Group on International Trade and Investment in Services (First Meeting, 1980 October 9), 1980-1981, 4 folders (Box 234, Folder 3 to 6)
    - Middle East Project (First Meeting, 1981 October 13), 2 folders
      - Correspondence and Papers, 1982-1983; 1 folder (Box 235, Folder 1)
      - Planning and Organization, 1983-1988; 1 folder (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - The China Factor: Sino-American Relations and the Global Issue (First Meeting, 1980 October 30), 1980-1981, 1 folder (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - Soviet Policy in Eastern Europe (First Meeting, 1981 January 8), 1980-1981, 2 folders (Box 235, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Journalists Discussion Group on Central America (First Meeting, 1981 January 13), 1980-1982, 1 folder (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - Discussion Group on Zimbabwe (First Meeting, 1981 January 29), 1980-1981, 1 folder (Box 235, Folder 7)
    - Divisive Forces in Canada (First Meeting, 1981 February 26), 1980-1981, 1 folder (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - International Banking and Financing (First Meeting, 1981 March 12), 1981-1983, 2 folders (Box 236, Folder 2 to 3)
    - Managing the U.S.-Soviet Relationship (First Meeting, 1981 April 16), 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box 236, Folder 4 to 5)
    - United States Industrial Policy (First Meeting, 1981 April 23), 1980-1982, 4 folders (Box 237, Folder 1 to 4)
    - United States Conventional Forces in the 1980s (First Meeting, 1981 May 12), 1980-1982, 1 folder (Box 237, Folder 5)
    - United States Conventional Forces in the 1980s (First Meeting, 1981 May 12), 1980-1982, 1 folder (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - Strategic Arms and American Security (First Meeting, 1981 May 14), 1981-1983, 2 folders (Box 238, Folder 2 to 3)
    - Executive-Congressional Relations and Foreign Policy (First Meeting, 1981 September 15), 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box 238, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Middle East (First Meeting, 1981 October 13), 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box 239, Folder 1 to 2)
    - United States Policy on International Information Flows (First Meeting, 1981 October 13), 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box 239, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Prospects for Change in South Africa (First Meeting, 1981 November 24), 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box 239, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Indochina (First Meeting, 1981 December 1), 1981, 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 1)
    - Economic Summitry (First Meeting, 1981 December 14), 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box 240, Folder 2 to 3)
    - North Africa (First Meeting, 1982 January 7), 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box 240, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Eastern Europe and the Polish Crisis (First Meeting, 1982 January 25), 1981-1982, 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 6)
    - Internal Developments Within the Soviet Union (First Meeting, 1982 March 8), 1981-1983, 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 7)
    - The Iranian Hostage Crisis in Retrospect: Implications for the Future (First Meeting, 1982 March 30), 2 boxes
      - Correspondence, 1981-1982; 2 folders (Box 241, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Correspondence, 1983; 3 folders (Box 241, Folder 3 to 5)
      - Meetings, 1982-1983; 6 folders (Box 242, Folder 1 to 6)
    - Latin American Immigration (First Meeting, 1982 March 30), 1981-1985, 4 folders (Box 243, Folder 1 to 4)
    - El Salvador and Extraterritoriality (First Meeting, 1982 April 21), 1982, 1 folder (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - Internationalization of Banking (First Meeting, 1982 April 22), 1981-1982, 1 folder (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - United States and Japan (First Meeting, 1982 May 6), 1981-1983, 2 folders (Box 244, Folder 2 to 3)
    - Canadian-American Relations (First Meeting, 1982 October 20), 1982-1984, 1 folder (Box 244, Folder 4)
    - Israel (First Meeting, 1982 October 25), 1982-1984, 2 folders (Box 244, Folder 5 to 6)
    - The China Group (First Meeting, 1982 October 26), 1981-1985, 2 folders (Box 245, Folder 1 to 2)
    - United States Government-Business Relations (First Meeting, 1983 January 12), 1982-1984, 3 folders (Box 245, Folder 3 to 5)
    - East-West Technology Trade, Meeting with the Office of Technology Assessment, 1983 January 25; 1 folder (Box 245, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Union and the Reagan Administration (First Meeting, 1983 January 31), 1982-1984, 2 folders (Box 245, Folder 7 to 8)
    - United States-Cuba Relations (First Meeting, 1983 February 15), 1982-1984, 3 folders (Box 246, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Stability in the Gulf (First Meeting, 1983 March 8), 1982-1984, 1 folder (Box 246, Folder 4)
    - European-American Relations (First Meeting, 1983 April 4), 1982-1984, 1 folder (Box 246, Folder 5)
    - European-American Relations (First Meeting, 1983 April 4), 1982-1984, 2 folders (Box 247, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Arms Control and Space Weapons Technology, Meeting with the Office of Technology Assessment, 1983 June 20; 1 folder (Box 247, Folder 3)
    - Central America (First Meeting, 1983 September 21), 1983-1984, 1 folder (Box 247, Folder 4)
    - Egypt (First Meeting, 1983 October 31), 1983-1985, 2 folders (Box 247, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Soviet Union's "Extended Empire" (First Meeting, 1983 November 10), 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 248, Folder 1 to 2)
    - International Banking and U.S. Foreign Policy (First Meeting, 1983 December 8), 1983-1985, 2 folders (Box 248, Folder 3 to 4)
    - United States Trade and Adjustment Policies (First Meeting, 1984 January 23), 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 248, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Turkey (First Meeting, 1984 January 26), 1983-1985, 2 folders (Box 249, Folder 1 to 2)
    - United States-Canada Relations (First Meeting, 1984 February 27), 1984, 3 folders (Box 249, Folder 3 to 5)
    - U.S. Policy Toward Antarctica (First Meeting, 1984 March 7), 1983-1987, 3 folders (Box 250, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Insuring Commercial Bank Loans to Debtor Countries (First Meeting, 1984 April 19), 1984, 1 folder (Box 250, Folder 4)
    - Israel (First Meeting, 1984 April 25), 1984, 1 folder (Box 250, Folder 5)
    - Advanced Developing Countries, Latin America (First Meeting, 1984 May 8), 1983-1985, 1 folder (Box 250, Folder 6)
    - Working Group Dinner on the Role of International Law in Foreign Policy, 1984 June 11; 1 folder (Box 250, Folder 7)
    - Jordan (First Meeting, 1984 December 6), 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box 251, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Arab Radicalism (First Meeting, 1984 December 12), 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box 251, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Military Trips, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 251, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Studies Program Seminars (First Meeting, 1985 January 7), 1985-1986, 1 folder (Box 251, Folder 6)
    - John J. McCloy Study Group on Eastern Europe (First Meeting, 1985 January 10), 1984-1985, 1 folder (Box 251, Folder 7)
    - John J. McCloy Study Group on Eastern Europe (First Meeting, 1985 January 10), 1984-1985, 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 1)
    - Seminar on Expanding Technology Transfer Between the United States and Japan, with the Japan Society, 1985 February 6; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 2)
    - Study Group on United States – Japan Labor Issues (First Meeting, 1985 February 7), 1984-1985, 3 folders (Box 252, Folder 3 to 5)
    - International Law and the Use of Force (First Meeting, 1985 February 28), 1984-1988, 2 boxes (1 partial)
      - Correspondence, 1984-1988; 2 folders (Box 253, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Meetings and Papers, 1984-1988; 3 folders (Box 253, Folder 3 to 5)
      - Meetings and Papers, 1984-1988; 2 folders (Box 254, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Miscellaneous Reading Materials, 1985; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 3)
    - Korea Study Group, and Ad Hoc Discussion Group on Japan (First Meeting, 1985 March 11), 1985, 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 4)
    - Ad Hoc Meeting on China, 1985 March 13; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 5)
    - Study Group on TV News and American Foreign Policy (First Meeting, 1985 March 15), portions of 2 boxes
      - Correspondence, Notes, Planning, 1984-1986; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 6)
      - Meetings, 1985; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 7)
      - Meetings, 1985; 2 folders (Box 255, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Studies Program Seminar in Honor of the Study Group on Improved US-Japan Communication and Understanding, 1985 March 25; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 3)
    - Conference on the Impact of Vietnam on American Foreign Policy, 1985 April 15; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 4)
    - Author's Review Group on Stalson, Helena, "Effects of Foreign Government Policies on U.S. International Competitiveness in Services", 1985 April 18; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 5)
    - Studies Events (First Meeting, 1985 April 23), 1985-1987, 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 6)
    - Studies Program Seminar in Honor of Salvador Lopez, 1985 April 30; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 7)
    - The Future of the World Trading System and the Challenges for U.S. Trade Policy, Steering Committee (First Meeting, 1985 May 6), 1985-1988, 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 8)
    - The Future of the World Trading System and the Challenges for U.S. Trade Policy, Steering Committee (First Meeting, 1985 May 6), 1985-1988, 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - Committee on African Development Strategies, Bellagio Conference, 1985 May 10-12; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 2)
    - Ad Hoc Meeting on Japan, 1985 May 29; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 3)
    - Ross, Robert, Fluidity and Ambiguity in Indochina: the Kampuchean Civil War and Prospects for Settlement, 1985 May; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - Seung-chul, Ahn, Korea's Perspective on Trade Tensions in the Pacific, 1985 May; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - Development in Ethiopia and United States Policy toward the Horn of Africa (First Meeting, 1985 July 18), 1985, 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - Comparative Studies of Labor in Japan and in the United States-, East-West Center, Honolulu (Conference Date, 1985 August 15-17), 1984-1985, 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 7)
    - Studies Program Seminar in Honor of African Diplomatic Group, 1985 August 22; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 8)
    - Studies Program Seminar in Honor of Saburo Tsukamoto, 1985 September 11; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 9)
    - Studies Program Seminar in Honor of Chinese Specialists on the Soviet Union, 1985 October 28; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 10)
    - Studies Program Seminar in Honor of the Institute of International Relations, Taiwan, 1985 December 2; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 11)
    - Studies Program Seminar on the Philippines, 1985 December 10; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 12)
    - Study Group on U.S.-U.S.S.R. Relations (First Meeting, 1985 December 11), 1985-1986, 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 13)
    - Study Group on International Corporate Alliances and the Future of Global Competition and Cooperation (First Meeting, 1985 December 16), 1985-1992, 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 14)
    - Study Group on United States Policy Toward South Africa (First Meeting, 1986 January 13), 9 folders
      - Background Papers, 1986; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 1)
      - Meetings, 1986 January 13-December 1; 6 folders
        - First Meeting, 1986 January 13; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 2)
        - Second Meeting, 1986 February 26; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 3)
        - Third Meeting, 1986 March 24; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 4)
        - Fourth Meeting, 1986 April 14; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 5)
        - Fifth Meeting, 1986 May 12; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 6)
        - Sixth Meeting, 1986 December 1; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 7)
      - Membership, 1985; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 9)
    - Study Group on Arabia after the Oil Boom: Political and Security Consequences of Economic Contraction in the Gulf and Peninsula States (First Meeting, 1986 January 29), 1985-1986, 2 folders (Box 257, Folder 10 to 11)
    - United States-Japan Relations (First Meeting, 1986 February 4), 1985-1986, 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 12)
    - United States-Japan Relations (First Meeting, 1986 February 4), 1985-1986, 2 folders (Box 258, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Review Group on Post-Mao Reform in China (First Meeting, 1986 February 12), 1986-1987, 3 folders (Box 258, Folder 3 to 5)
    - Asia Crisis Core Group (First Meeting, 1986 February 18), 4 folders
      - Philippines, 1986 February 18; 1 folder (Box 258, Folder 6)
      - Korea, 1986 March 19; 1 folder (Box 258, Folder 7)
      - Pakistan, 1986 April 15; 1 folder (Box 258, Folder 8)
      - Southeast Asia, 1986 May 28; 1 folder (Box 258, Folder 9)
    - Author's Review Group on Chang, Parris, "On the Future of Taiwan" (First Meeting, 1986 February 24), 1985-1987, 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - World Financial Markets (First Meeting, 1986 March 20), 1985-1986, 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 2)
    - Trade Group-Miscellaneous (First Meeting, ), 1986 March 27; 2 folders
      - 1984-1986, 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 3)
      - 1986-1991, 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 4)
    - Conference on Social Change in Japan and the United States and Its Impact on Bilateral Relations (Conference Date, 1986 May 16-17), 2 folders
      - Articles, Lists, Notes, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence and Papers, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 6)
    - Privatization (First Meeting, 1986 June 17), 1986-1988, 2 folders (Box 260, Folder 1 to 2)
    - United States Agricultural Trade Policy (First Meeting, 1986 June 19), 1986, 2 folders (Box 260, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Author's Review Group on Ranneberger, Michael E., Manuscript on Namibia and Angola, 1986 June 24; more than 2 folders
      - Correspondence, 1986; 1 folder (Box 260, Folder 5)
      - Manuscript, 1986; 2 folders (Box 260, Folder 6 to 7)
    - Prospects for Peace and Stability in Indochina (First Meeting, 1986 September 24), 1986-1987, 1 folder (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - Authors' Discussion Group, Oksenberg and Jacobsen, "China's Early Years in the World Bank and International Monetary Fund: An Appraisal", 1986 October 15; 1 folder (Box 261, Folder 2)
    - Discussion Group on Iran (First Meeting, 1986 October 28), 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 261, Folder 3 to 4)
    - West Coast Study Group on Mexico/Central America (First Meeting, 1986 October 30), 1986-1987, 1 folder (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - United States-Canada Trade Negotiations (First Meeting, 1986 December 4), 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 261, Folder 6 to 7)
    - United States-Canada Trade Negotiations (First Meeting, 1986 December 4), 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 262, Folder 1 to 2)
    - John J. McCloy Discussion Group on National Objectives and Priorities in American Foreign Policy (First Meeting, 1986 December 15), 1986-1987, 3 folders (Box 262, Folder 3 to 5)
    - Studies Seminars and Discussion Groups, 1986-1988; 2 folders (Box 263, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Discussion Group on the Proposed Vatican Book Project, 1987 January 5; 2 folders (Box 263, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Study Group on Military Force Projection: Its Current and Future Role in U.S. National Security Strategy (First Meeting, 1987 January 14), 1986-1987, 1 folder (Box 263, Folder 5)
    - Arms Control Agenda of the Next Administration (First Meeting, 1987 January 19), 1987-1988, 1 folder (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - Discussion Group on Israel in Transition: Internal Politics and the Peace Process (First Meeting, 1987 February 3), 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 263, Folder 7 to 8)
    - Study Group on Capital Constraints on Developing Countries (First Meeting, 1987 February 24), 1987, 1 folder (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Study Group on Korea (First Meeting, 1987 February 26), more than 6 folders
      - Correspondence, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 264, Folder 2)
      - Digests, 1987; 2 folders (Box 264, Folder 3 to 4)
      - Funding, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 264, Folder 5)
      - Report, 1987 August; 1 folder (Box 264, Folder 6)
      - Rosters, 1987; 1 folder (Box 264, Folder 7)
      - Trip, Biographies, 1987; 1 folder (Box 264, Folder 8)
    - Technological Change and Foreign Policy (First Meeting, 1987 March 4), 1981-1989, 1 folder (Box 264, Folder 9)
    - Technological Change and Foreign Policy (First Meeting, 1987 March 4), 1981-1989, 2 folders (Box 265, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Study Group on Privatization (First Meeting, 1987 March 5), 1986-1987, 1 folder (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - "Disaster! The United Nations and International Relief Management," Study by Schmitz, Charles A, 1987 March; 1 folder (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - Current Developments in the USSR (First Meeting, 1987 April 8), 1987, 1 folder (Box 265, Folder 5)
    - Polish-American Roundtable, Warsaw, 1987 May 4-8, 2 folders (Box 265, Folder 6 to 7)
    - Henry A. Kissinger Study Group on Soviet Approaches to Arms Control (First Meeting, 1987 May 27), 1987-1989, 2 folders (Box 266, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Author's Review Group, "Jewish Fundamentalism in Israel", 1987 June 2; 2 folders (Box 266, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Study Group on the Philippines Bases (First Meeting, 1987 June 22), portions of 2 boxes
      - Book Distribution and Press Briefing, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 266, Folder 5)
      - Conference, U.S.-Philippines Bases Agreement: Looking to the Future, 1988 February 15-18; 1 folder (Box 266, Folder 6)
      - Digests, 1987; 1 folder (Box 266, Folder 7)
      - Planning, 1986-1989; 1 folder (Box 266, Folder 8)
      - Proposal and Planning, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - Western Attitudes Toward the Soviet Union (First Meeting, 1987 September 27), 1987-1988, 1 folder (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - Study Group on Conventional Defense and Arms Control in Europe (First Meeting, 1987 October 22), 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box 267, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Study Group on Soviet Policy in Asia (First Meeting, 1987 October 29), 2 folders
      - Digests, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 267, Folder 5)
      - Planning, 1987; 1 folder (Box 267, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Union in the International Economy (First Meeting, 1987 November 9), 1987-1988, 1 folder (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Europe and America: Issues for the 1990s (First Meeting, 1987 November 16), 1987, 1 folder (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - Study Group on Brazil (First Meeting, 1988 March 14), 1987-1988, 1 folder (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - Study Group on Cuba (First Meeting, 1988 April 6), 1987-1990, 1 folder (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - Study Group on Japan's Role in International Financial and Developmental Institutions (First Meeting, 1988 May 18), 1987-1988, 1 folder (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - Study Group on Defense Budget and Issues (First Meeting, 1988 June 22), 1988, 1 folder (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - U.S.-Japan Symposium: Maui Conference, 1988 June 27-28; 1 folder (Box 268, Folder 7)
    - Study Group on Defense Issues and Budgets (First Meeting, 1988 July 20), 1988, 1 folder (Box 268, Folder 8)
    - Conference on U.S. Japanese Relations, with the Asia-Pacific Association of Japan, Maui, Hawaii, 1988 August 22-23; 5 folders
      - American Papers, 1988; 1 folder (Box 269, Folder 1)
      - Japanese Papers, 1988; 1 folder (Box 269, Folder 2)
      - List, 1988; 1 folder (Box 269, Folder 3)
      - Planning, 1988; 1 folder (Box 269, Folder 4)
      - Report, 1988; 1 folder (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - Discussion Group on Indochina (First Meeting, 1988 October 17), 3 folders
      - Background Papers, 1988-1990; 1 folder (Box 269, Folder 6)
      - Rapporteur's Reports, 1988-1990; 1 folder (Box 269, Folder 7)
      - Trip, 1989 February 25-March 13, 1 folder (Box 269, Folder 8)
    - Future of the U.S.-Canadian Free Trade Agreement (First Meeting, 1988 October 31), 1988-1989, 1 folder (Box 269, Folder 9)
    - Study Seminar on the Twin Goals of Security and Arms Control: Twelve Suggestions for a More Comprehensive Policy in the Far East, 1988 November 1; 1 folder (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Policy Roundtable (First Meeting, 1988 December 1), 2 folders
      - 1988-1990, 1 folder (Box 270, Folder 2)
      - 1990-1991, 1 folder (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - CFR/NIRA/Japan Center for International Exchange Conference on Social Change in Japan and the United States and its Impact on Bilateral Relations, 1988 December 10-11; 1 folder (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - Henry A. Kissinger Discussion Group on Eastern Europe (First Meeting, 1988 December 13), 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 270, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Foreign Policy Roundtable Seminar Meetings (First Meeting, 1988 December 21), 4 boxes (2 partial)
      - 1988-1989, 1 folder (Box 270, Folder 7)
      - China and America: Beyond the Big Chill, 1989 October 12; 1 folder (Box 271, Folder 1)
      - The United Nations Reborn: Conflict Control in the Post-Cold War World, 1989 November 8; 1 folder (Box 271, Folder 2)
      - The Implications of Scientific and Technological Change for American Foreign Policy, 1989 December 5; 1 folder (Box 271, Folder 3)
      - The Defense Debate, 1990 January 25; 1 folder (Box 271, Folder 4)
      - 1989 and All That, 1990 March 28, 1 folder (Box 271, Folder 5)
      - Cuba's Cloudy Future, 1990 May 31; 1 folder (Box 271, Folder 6)
      - Why We Will Soon Miss the Cold War, 1990 October 10; 1 folder (Box 271, Folder 7)
      - The Future of Force and American Security, 1990 November 27; 1 folder (Box 271, Folder 8)
      - Concerts, Collective Security, and the Future of Europe, 1990 December 19; 1 folder (Box 271, Folder 9)